<resources>
    <string name="app_name">easyManager</string>
    <string name="tips">tips</string>
    <string name="isrootmodestr">Now is root user  , and auto active app to  root mode .</string>
    <string name="general_tips">Tips [ General Mode ]</string>
    <string name="general_tips_str_head">"The software cannot be used normally in the current environment. (If you have a lower version of Android, please switch to magisk when using root authorization, otherwise you can only use adb mode and cannot activate root mode)\n\nPlease run the following script through adb to activate adb mode:\n\n sh  "</string>
    <string name="general_tips_str_end">\nOnce the activation script has been successfully executed, click Exit from the top right corner of the software and reopen the software.\n</string>
    <string name="options_menu_help_str">Help</string>
    <string name="options_menu_full_exit">Force Exit</string>
    <string name="options_menu_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="show_help_title">Help Document</string>
    <string name="show_help_getAppPermissonHELP">\nThis interface is used to control the permissions of the program, because since Android 5, the permissions of the program have been taken over by AppOPS, so everything done here is based on the IAppOpsService service.\n\n1. The menu in the upper right corner can get the application of the current device administrator.\n        2. The left side shows the permission names with Chinese, they are a whole, allowing you to operate multiple permissions or permission groups at once.\n        3. On the right is the case of configuring permissions, you can choose default, deny, allow, ignore, etc., which may not take effect immediately, and need to rely on the special nature of the customized operating system.\n        4. There is an option in the lower left corner, which allows you to select a batch or a single application to change the permissions.\n        5. In the lower right corner is the button to change permissions, all operations will be done here.\n        6. Click on the program entry in the list, it will automatically jump to the program information interface, this part needs to be in ROOT mode to use normally.\n        7. The magnifying glass on the left side of the above menu is used to retrieve the application, and the corresponding program list can be retrieved by entering Chinese and English.\n        8. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getAppInfoHELP">\nThis interface is used to manage the services, active items, and broadcast receiver components of a single application, and the functional implementation here is based on the IPackageManager service, which requires the ROOT mode.\n\n1. The menu in the upper right corner can get the detailed information of each component of the current program.\n        2. The options in the lower left corner can select batches and individual entries to perform change operations.\n        3. After the button in the lower right corner is clicked, the corresponding rule will be executed.\n        4. The magnifying glass on the left side of the above menu is used to retrieve applications, and the corresponding program list can be retrieved by entering Chinese and English.\n        5. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\nPS: The switches of some entries may show errors, but they are working and executing normally, click the switch, the status becomes off, the closed operation will be performed normally, the status becomes on, it will become the open operation, you can use it with confidence.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getAppDsiableCompentHELP">\nThis interface is used to disable, close, and freeze programs, and is based on the IPackageManager service.\n\n1. The menu in the upper right corner can get the program of the current host administrator.\n        2. The option on the right can choose to enable or disable the app.\n        3. There is an option in the lower left corner, which allows you to operate in batches and in a single selection.\n        4. The button in the bottom right corner will execute the rule parameters you have selected before.\n        5. Click on the program entry in the list, it will automatically jump to the program information interface, this part needs to be in ROOT mode to use normally.\n        6. The magnifying glass on the left side of the above menu is used to retrieve the application, enter Chinese and English to retrieve the corresponding program list.\n        7. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getAppFirewallHELP">\nThis interface is used to manage the program network, and is implemented based on invoking system commands, which must be in ROOT mode.\n\n1. The menu in the upper right corner can get the program of the host administrator.\n        2. On the right, you can choose to allow or disable the network.\n        3. In the lower left corner, you can select batch or single item to control the network.\n        4. The button in the lower right corner, after being clicked, will execute the corresponding rules and parameters.\n        5. Click on the program entry in the list, it will automatically jump to the program information interface, this part needs to be in ROOT mode to use normally.\n        6. The magnifying glass on the left side of the above menu is used to retrieve the application, enter Chinese and English to retrieve the corresponding program list.\n        7. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getAppInstallLocalFileHELP">\nThis interface is used to install local apk packages and is implemented based on the IPackageManager service.\n\n1. The menu in the upper right corner can get the program of the host administrator.\n        2. On the right, you can choose the local apk program installation package file, or you can choose the local work folder to store the installation package.\n        3. In the lower left corner, you can select batch and single item.\n        4. The button in the lower right corner, after being clicked, will execute the corresponding rules and parameters.\n        5. Click on the program entry in the list, it will automatically jump to the program information interface, this part needs to be in ROOT mode to use normally.\n        6. The magnifying glass on the left side of the above menu is used to retrieve the application, enter Chinese and English to retrieve the corresponding program list.\n        7. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getAppDumpHELP">\nThis interface is used to extract the local program installation files, and is implemented based on the system API service.\n\n1. The menu in the upper right corner can get the program of the host administrator.\n        2. You can choose the package name, program name, and extraction time on the right, which is used to save the extracted program installation files, and the extracted files are stored in the /easyManager/dump folder under the internal storage.\n        3. In the lower left corner, you can select batch and single item.\n        4. The button in the lower right corner, after being clicked, will execute the corresponding rules and parameters.\n        5. Click on the program entry in the list, it will automatically jump to the program information interface, this part needs to be in ROOT mode to use normally.\n        6. The magnifying glass on the left side of the above menu is used to retrieve the application, enter Chinese and English to retrieve the corresponding program list.\n        7. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getUninstallHELP">\nThis interface is used to delete local programs and is implemented based on the IPackageManager service.\n\n1. The menu in the upper right corner can get the program of the host administrator.\n        2. In the lower left corner, you can choose batch and single item.\n        3. The button in the lower right corner, after being clicked, will execute the corresponding rules and parameters.\n        4. Click on the program entry in the list, it will automatically jump to the program information interface, this part needs to be in ROOT mode to use normally.\n        5. The magnifying glass on the left side of the above menu is used to retrieve the application, and the corresponding program list can be retrieved by entering Chinese and English.\n        6. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getAppClenProcessHELP">\nThis interface is used to terminate the daemon and is implemented based on the IActivityManager service.\n\n1. The menu in the upper right corner can get the program of the host administrator.\n        2. In the lower left corner, you can choose batch and single item.\n        3. The button in the lower right corner, after being clicked, will execute the corresponding rules and parameters.\n        4. Click on the program entry in the list, it will automatically jump to the program information interface, this part needs to be in ROOT mode to use normally.\n        5. The magnifying glass on the left side of the above menu is used to retrieve the application, and the corresponding program list can be retrieved by entering Chinese and English.\n        6. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getAppBackupHELP">\nThis interface is used to back up locally installed programs and is implemented based on the system API service.\n\n1. The menu in the upper right corner can get the program of the host administrator.\n        2. There are three options on the left, providing three backup methods.\n        3. There are three options on the right, providing three compression formats for backup.\n        4. In the lower left corner, you can choose batch and single item.\n        5. The button in the lower right corner, after being clicked, will execute the corresponding rules and parameters.\n        6. Click on the program entry in the list, it will automatically jump to the program information interface, this part needs to be in ROOT mode to use normally.\n        7. The magnifying glass on the left side of the above menu is used to retrieve the application, and the corresponding program list can be retrieved by entering Chinese and English.\n        8. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getAppRestoryHELP">\nThis interface is used to restore the local backup program, based on the system API service implementation, before using this function, you should first in Magisk or SuperUSER, switch the root mount mode to global, otherwise there will be software data recovery failure.\n\n1. The menu in the upper right corner can get the program of the host administrator.\n        2. There are three options on the left that provide three recovery methods.\n        3. There are three options on the right to provide three compression formats to use when recovering.\n        4. In the lower left corner, you can choose batch and single item.\n        5. The button in the lower right corner, after being clicked, will execute the corresponding rules and parameters.\n        6. Click on the program entry in the list, it will automatically jump to the program information interface, this part needs to be in ROOT mode to use normally.\n        7. The magnifying glass on the left side of the above menu is used to retrieve the application, and the corresponding program list can be retrieved by entering Chinese and English.\n        8. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getMountLocalImgHELP">\nThis interface is used to mount the local image file to the computer, based on the system API service implementation, must be ROOT mode.\n\n1. Click the button to scan the local image to get all the image files in the device.\n        2. There are four mount options in the bottom left corner.\n        3. The button in the lower right corner, after being clicked, will execute the corresponding rules and parameters, and hang the local image on the computer for use.\n        4. The magnifying glass on the left side of the above menu is used to retrieve documents, and the corresponding file list can be retrieved by entering Chinese and English.\n        5. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getCreateImgHELP">\nThis interface is used to create a local image file, which is implemented based on the system API service, and must be in ROOT mode.\n\n1. The first edit box on the left needs to enter the name of a mirror document, you can name it arbitrarily.\n        2. On the right is the selected file suffix.\n        3. There is a numerical edit box in the lower left corner, which requires you to fill in the file size, and try to use integers.\n        4. There is a file size unit in the bottom right corner, you need to select one.\n        5. Click the button below to execute the corresponding rules and parameters.\n        6. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getSetNTPHELP">\nThis interface is used to configure the local NTP server address, which is implemented based on the system shell service.\n\n1. The first edit box on the left needs to enter a self-NTP server address.\n        2. On the right is to select the NTP server address that comes with the program.\n        3. Click the button to execute the corresponding rules and parameters.\n        4. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getSetRateHELP">\nThis interface is used to configure the device refresh rate value, which is implemented based on the system shell service.\n\n1. In the second edit box on the left, you need to enter a refresh rate value of your own.\n        2. On the right is the refresh rate value that comes with the program.\n        3. Click the button to execute the corresponding rules and parameters.\n        4. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getDelXHELP">\nThis interface is used to remove the x mark of the WIFI or cellular coal network, and is implemented based on the system shell service.\n\n        1. Click the button to execute the corresponding rules and parameters.\n        2. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getFileSharedHELP">\nThis interface is used to share device files and is implemented based on the system API service.\n\n1. Click the Add File button, the files in the local internal storage will be listed, check the files or folders that need to be shared, click OK, and the checked ones will be added to the sharing list.\n        2. Click the Add Shared Program button, the programs installed by the host administrator will be listed, check the programs that need to be shared, click Confirm, and the checked ones will be added to the shared list.\n        3. There is a numerical edit box in the upper right corner, if the default port provided by the program is occupied, you can enter a numerical value by yourself, to replace the default port of the program, you need to re-share.\n        4. Click the Start Share button to start sharing the content in the list.\n        5. The person being shared only needs to enter the network address and port displayed by the program in the browser to access the content of the shared list.\n        6. Click on the icon in the top left corner to go back to the previous menu.\n\n</string>
    <string name="show_help_getMainHelp">\neasyManager is an Android system management tool, which has the advantages of lightweight, functional core, and simplicity, and also allows the sharing of API interfaces with third-party application authorization.\n\neasyManager only does what it needs to do, it doesn\'t always reside in the background services, only the core services are running.\n\nThere are three large buttons distributed below the home page.\n            The first button on the left is used to control the list of applications that have been connected to easyManager SDK, the button is closed, that is, the application has been revoked, and the easyManager function interface can no longer be used, the button is opened, which means that the application has passed the authorization and can call the easyManager function interface.\n            The middle button is the functional area that can be used to operate the machine\'s applications and other functions.\n            The third button gives a more detailed introduction to the easyManager tool.\n\nFor more help, please click on the help word in the upper right corner to get it.\n\nClick Exit in the upper right corner, only end the process of this application, will not terminate the SDK service process, next time you open it, you do not need to reactivate it again (if you do not restart the phone).\n        Click on the upper right corner to exit completely, the SDK service process and this application process will be terminated at the same time, and you need to reactivate it next time you open it.\n\n</string>
    <string name="get_all_apps">Getting all apps installed by the host administrator (including those that have been disabled by the organization, please wait...)</string>
    <string name="get_all_apps2">Fetching all apps installed by Host Manager (please wait...)</string>
    <string name="get_user_apps">Getting apps installed by the host administrator (including those that have been disabled by the organization, please wait...)</string>
    <string name="get_user_apps2">Getting host manager installed apps (please wait...)</string>
    <string name="get_all_disable_apps">Getting apps that are blocked by the host administrator (please wait...)</string>
    <string name="get_local_apps">Fetching the host\'s app (please wait...)</string>
    <string name="get_all_process_app">Fetching all running applications (including host system programs) from the host administrator, please wait...)</string>
    <string name="get_user_process_app">Fetching all running apps from the host administrator (please wait...)</string>
    <string name="scanner_local_img">Retrieving image files owned by the host administrator (please wait...)</string>
    <string name="execute_cmd">Running command for host manager (please wait...)</string>
    <string name="get_app_permission">Getting all the permissions for this app...</string>
    <string name="get_app_service">Getting the service object that this app has...</string>
    <string name="get_app_activity">Getting the activity items that this app has...</string>
    <string name="get_app_receiver">Getting the broadcast service owned by this app...</string>
    <string name="apply_app_permission_title">Permission modification is being made to the process, please wait...</string>
    <string name="apply_app_permission_msg">"The procedures that are currently modifying the permissions are: %s "</string>
    <string name="apply_app_compat_title">The process is being modified to the group status, please wait...</string>
    <string name="apply_app_compat_msg">"The process in which the part status is being modified is: %s "</string>
    <string name="apply_app_network_title">Network state modification is being made to the process, please wait...</string>
    <string name="apply_app_network_msg">"The processes that are modifying the state of the network are: %s "</string>
    <string name="apply_app_install_title">Installing process, please wait...</string>
    <string name="apply_app_install_msg">"The programs that are currently being accepted for installation are: %s "</string>
    <string name="apply_app_uninstall_title">Deleting process, please wait...</string>
    <string name="apply_app_uninstall_msg">"The procedures that are currently being accepted for removal are: %s "</string>
    <string name="apply_app_restory_title">Restoring the backup program, please wait...</string>
    <string name="apply_app_restory_msg">"The backup files that are currently being restored are: %s "</string>
    <string name="apply_app_backup_title">Backup operation is being carried out on the program, please wait...</string>
    <string name="apply_app_backup_msg">"The procedures that are currently being accepted for backup are: %s "</string>
    <string name="apply_app_process_title">Terminating a program running by the host manager, wait...</string>
    <string name="apply_app_process_msg">"The procedures currently being terminated are: %s "</string>
    <string name="apply_app_dump_title">Extracting the program, please wait...</string>
    <string name="apply_app_dump_msg">"The procedures that are currently being extracted are: %s "</string>
    <string name="now_search_ing_msg">Retrieving (please wait...)</string>
    <string name="its_ok_msg">The run has been completed, please refresh it manually.</string>
    <string name="error_tips">Error</string>
    <string name="scan_local_backup_file_msg">Retrieving backup document for host manager (please wait...)</string>
    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="menu_scan_local_backup_file">Scanner Local Backup Files</string>
    <string name="menu_scan_get_all_process">Get all process</string>
    <string name="menu_scan_get_user_process">Get user process</string>
    <string name="menu_get_app_permission">Get permission</string>
    <string name="menu_get_app_service">Get services</string>
    <string name="menu_get_app_activity">Get activitys</string>
    <string name="menu_get_app_recvi">Get broadcasts</string>
    <string name="menu_get_all_app">Get all app (include disable app)</string>
    <string name="menu_get_all_app2">Get all app</string>
    <string name="menu_get_user_all_app">Get user app (include disable app)</string>
    <string name="menu_get_user_all_app2">Get user app</string>
    <string name="menu_get_user_all_disable_app">Get disable app</string>
    <string name="is_copy_ok">Copied</string>
    <string name="text_home_app_manage">Application management</string>
    <string name="text_home_process_manage">Background process management</string>
    <string name="text_home_backup_and_restory_manage">Backup and recovery of applications</string>
    <string name="text_home_usb_flash_drive_mode">USB flash disk mode</string>
    <string name="text_home_other_tool">Other tool</string>
    <string name="edit_hint_input_file_name">Please input file name</string>
    <string name="edit_hint_input_file_size">Please input file size</string>
    <string name="edit_hint_share_address">Share IP</string>
    <string name="edit_hint_share_port">Share Port</string>
    <string name="button_apply_chagne">Apply Change</string>
    <string name="button_apply">Apply</string>
    <string name="button_start_create">Create</string>
    <string name="button_add_share_file">Add Share File</string>
    <string name="button_add_share_app">Add Share Application</string>
    <string name="button_start_share">Start Share</string>
    <string name="button_home_permission">Permissions Manage</string>
    <string name="button_home_disable">Suspend / Disable</string>
    <string name="button_home_network">Network Manage</string>
    <string name="button_home_install_local_file">Install Local File</string>
    <string name="button_home_dump_app">Extract App</string>
    <string name="button_home_uninstall">Uninstall App</string>
    <string name="button_home_process_clean">Clean Process</string>
    <string name="button_home_backup">Backup APP</string>
    <string name="button_home_restory">Restory APP</string>
    <string name="button_home_use_usb_mode">Mount Local Image File</string>
    <string name="button_home_create_usb_img_file">Create Image File</string>
    <string name="button_home_set_ntp">Set NTP Service</string>
    <string name="button_home_set_rate">Modify Rate</string>
    <string name="button_home_del_x">Fix Signal X</string>
    <string name="button_home_file_share">File Share</string>
    <string name="query_hint_str">Please enter your search</string>
    <string name="usb_button_scan_local_img">Scanner Local Image File</string>
    <string name="usb_button_mount_img">Mount</string>
    <string name="spin_item_phone_sms">Phone And SMS</string>
    <string name="spin_item_storage">Storage</string>
    <string name="spin_item_clipboard">"Clipboard "</string>
    <string name="spin_item_battery">"Battery "</string>
    <string name="spin_item_background">Background</string>
    <string name="spin_item_camera_microphone">Camera And Microphone</string>
    <string name="spin_item_location">"Location "</string>
    <string name="spin_item_calendar">Calendar</string>
    <string name="spin_item_sensor">"Sensor "</string>
    <string name="spin_item_notify">Notify</string>
    <string name="spin_item_biometrics">Biometrics</string>
    <string name="spin_item_alert">Alert Window</string>
    <string name="spin_item_accessibility">Accessibillity</string>
    <string name="spin_item_account">Account</string>
    <string name="spin_item_write_settings">Write Settings</string>
    <string name="spin_item_read_device_id">Read Device Id</string>
    <string name="spin_item_app_standby">Standby</string>
    <string name="spin_item_app_standby_activity">Standby Bucket</string>
    <string name="spin_item_opt1_default">Default</string>
    <string name="spin_item_opt1_ignore">Ignore</string>
    <string name="spin_item_opt1_deny">Deny</string>
    <string name="spin_item_opt1_allow">Allow</string>
    <string name="spin_item_opt1_foreground">Foreground</string>
    <string name="spin_item_opt2_active">Active</string>
    <string name="spin_item_opt2_work">Work</string>
    <string name="spin_item_opt2_frequent">Frequent</string>
    <string name="spin_item_opt2_rare">Rare</string>
    <string name="spin_item_opt2_restricted">Restricted</string>
    <string name="spin_item_opt3_allow">Allow</string>
    <string name="spin_item_opt3_denial">Denial</string>
    <string name="spin_item_enable">Enable</string>
    <string name="spin_item_disable">Disable</string>
    <string name="spin_item_network_disable">Disable Network</string>
    <string name="spin_item_network_enable">Enable Network</string>
    <string name="spin_item_select_local_file">Select PKG File</string>
    <string name="spin_item_select_local_dir">Select PKG Dir</string>
    <string name="spin_item_dump_pkgname">Package Name Save</string>
    <string name="spin_item_dump_appname">APP Name Save</string>
    <string name="spin_item_dump_timename">Now Time Save</string>
    <string name="spin_item_app_and_data">Data And Program</string>
    <string name="spin_item_data">Data</string>
    <string name="spin_item_app">Program</string>
    <string name="spin_item_selected">Selected</string>
    <string name="spin_item_no_selected">No Selected</string>
    <string name="spin_item_all_selected">All Selected</string>
    <string name="button_select">Select</string>
    <string name="button_dump_app">Extract APP</string>
    <string name="button_del_app">Uninstall APP</string>
    <string name="button_clean">Clean</string>
    <string name="button_backup">Backup</string>
    <string name="button_restory">Restory</string>
    <string name="not_support_5">Android 5 and below devices are not supported</string>
    <string name="del_app_tips_6">The current system version is lower than Android 6, the task of deleting the software will be terminated as a background process, please reactivate it manually. (root mode can ignore this issue)</string>
    <string name="not_installed_app">Not Installed the App</string>
    <string name="choice_install_file">Please Choice Need Install Program File</string>
    <string name="unknow_msg">Unknown</string>
    <string name="try_install_app">Install</string>
    <string name="need_root_or_adb_msg">This feature requires adb or root privileges to use!!</string>
    <string name="warning_tips">Warning</string>
    <string name="need_root_msg">This part must be in root mode to work properly!!</string>
    <string name="stop_edit">Now is Unavailable</string>
    <string name="input_custom_ntp_service">"Please Input Custom NTP Service "</string>
    <string name="apply_ntp_service">Apply NTP Chanage</string>
    <string name="input_custom_rate">Please input num in 48 ~ 165</string>
    <string name="apply_rate">Apply Rate Chanage</string>
    <string name="apply_del_x">Del X</string>
    <string name="fix_vacant">Please Fix Vacant!!!</string>
    <string name="default_port">"Default Port is :  "</string>
    <string name="now_is_file_share">Now Running File Shared</string>
    <string name="is_share_file_msg">File</string>
    <string name="is_share_app_msg">Application</string>
    <string name="now_get_ing_head">"Now scanner local "</string>
    <string name="now_get_ing_end">" , please wait (there may be no response, please be patient)...."</string>
    <string name="dialog_choice_text">Choice</string>
    <string name="dialog_sure_text">Sure</string>
    <string name="file_share_previous_text">Previous</string>
    <string name="dialog_cancel_text">Cancel</string>
    <string name="parm_error">Parm Error....</string>
    <string name="file_share_not_select_file">Not Chocie File !</string>
    <string name="file_share_start_download">Download</string>
    <string name="mount_local_img_item_auto">Auto Mount</string>
    <string name="mount_local_img_item_mode1">Mode 1</string>
    <string name="mount_local_img_item_mode2">Mode 2</string>
    <string name="mount_local_img_item_mode3">Mode 3</string>
    <string name="low_mem_device">Now this device is too under-configured, and there will be problems with the functionality of this interface!</string>
    <string name="help_question_1">What is easyManager</string>
    <string name="help_question_2">What are its advantages?</string>
    <string name="help_question_3">How does it work?</string>
    <string name="help_question_4">What is the difference between it and Shizuku?</string>
    <string name="help_question_1_reply">EasyManager is a lightweight, core, and easy-to-use Android system management tool that is perfect for use on native systems. It also supports old devices like Android 4.0, as well as new devices like Android 14. As you can see, it will not give up on any old devices that are still in use, and it will continue to support it. Although it may not be perfect at the beginning, it has an infinite future</string>
    <string name="help_question_2_reply">EasyManager supports both adb and root modes of operation, and as you can see, it also supports exposing its private API to any authorized application for access\nIt now provides batch permission management for applications, background process cleaning, silent software installation/uninstallation, individual application services/activities/broadcasting/permission management, application network control, backup and recovery, file sharing and other functions\nIt provides a large number of one click functions. You just need to read the help document, select the corresponding rule, and finally click the big button to complete your expectations</string>
    <string name="help_question_3_reply">The working principle of easyManager draws inspiration from Shizuku and AppOps. Similar to these two, easyManager also needs to open a separate backend process into the shell or root shell in order to function properly\nPerform TCP communication through Socket and perform corresponding operations</string>
    <string name="help_question_4_reply">Unlike Shizuku, EasyManager has expanded its support for Android 4.0 lower versions and also provides corresponding SDK development kit tools externally. Any third-party program that connects to the SDK can use EasyManager\'s complete and private functional interfaces through the SDK. Most commonly used functions do not require developers to implement them again. EasyManager has already been fully encapsulated, and developers only need to focus on the interface interaction part\nMoreover, the interface open to the public by EasyManager has been tested and supports Android 4.0 to Android 14. They work stably and normally</string>
    <string name="app_clone_menu">Software Cloning</string>
    <string name="app_clone_button">Software Cloning</string>
    <string name="app_clone_manager_button">Software Clone Management</string>
    <string name="app_clone_delete_button">Software Clone Remove</string>
    <string name="app_clone_input_size_hint_str">Please enter, maximum: %s</string>
    <string name="app_clone_button_default_str">Apply Changes</string>
    <string name="app_clone_button_start_clone_str">Start Clone</string>
    <string name="app_clone_button_manager_clone_change_str">Apply Changes</string>
    <string name="app_clone_button_delete_clone_str">Remove Clone App</string>
    <string name="app_clone_create_clone_title">Now creating new clone (please wait...)</string>
    <string name="app_clone_create_clone_msg">Now creating the %s th clone</string>
    <string name="app_clone_manager_clone_mode_str1">ADD</string>
    <string name="app_clone_manager_clone_mode_str2">DELETE</string>
    <string name="app_clone_delete_clone_title">The cloner user is being deleted now, please wait...</string>
    <string name="app_clone_delete_clone_msg">"The cloner user being deleted now is: %s "</string>
    <string name="app_clone_manager_clone_title">Currently %s a program to the clone user, please wait...</string>
    <string name="app_clone_manager_clone_msg">The program currently applying changes is: %s</string>
    <string name="app_clone_manager_clone_start_users_msg">Clone program users are being enabled now, please wait...</string>
    <string name="app_clone_manager_clone_query_users_msg">Retrieving local cloner users now, please wait...</string>
    <string name="now_server_check_msg">"NOW SERVER %s "</string>
    <string name="now_server_check_running_msg">IS %s MODE RUNNING</string>
    <string name="now_server_check_dead_msg">NOT RUNNING</string>
    <string name="now_server_read_auth_msg">Now getting local authorization details...</string>
    <string name="show_clone_user_installed_app">Get cloned user installed programs</string>
    <string name="show_clone_user_all_installed_app">Get all programs of cloned user</string>
    <string name="show_clone_user_uid">Get clone user UID</string>
    <string name="show_start_app_clone_user">Enable cloning users</string>
    <string name="show_help_getAppCloneHELP">This interface is mainly used to implement clone applications, because starting from Android 5.0, Google has made major reforms to Android\'s multi-user mechanism, allowing the use of other clone user programs under the main user.\n\n\n\n         1. The menu bar in the upper right corner can obtain the program corresponding to the current user\'s status.\n\n         2. The above edit box can be filled with an integer to generate a corresponding number of clone programs.\n\n         3. There is an option in the lower right corner that allows you to select programs in batches or individually for cloning operations.\n\n         4. Below is a button to start cloning program clones. Click it to have the selected or unselected program perform the cloning operation.\n\n         5. Next to the menu above is a search button, which can search the contents of the current program list. Press Enter to synchronize the search results to the current program list.\n\n         6. Click the pattern in the upper left corner to return to the previous menu.</string>
    <string name="show_help_getAppCloneManagerHELP">This interface is mainly used to manage cloned applications, because starting from Android 5.0, Google has made major reforms to Android\'s multi-user mechanism, allowing the use of other cloned user programs under the main user.\n\n\n\n         1. The menu bar in the upper right corner can obtain the program corresponding to the current user\'s status.\n\n         2. There is an option in the lower left corner for selecting the addition or deletion of clone programs.\n\n         3. There is an option in the lower right corner that allows you to select programs in batches or individually to add or delete them.\n\n         4. Below is the button to apply changes. Click it to allow selected or unselected programs and clone program users to perform add or delete operations.\n\n         5. Next to the menu above is a search button, which can search the contents of the current program list. Press Enter to synchronize the search results to the current program list.\n\n         6. Click the pattern in the upper left corner to return to the previous menu.</string>
    <string name="show_help_getAppCloneRemoveHELP">This interface is mainly used to delete cloned applications, because starting from Android 5.0, Google has made major reforms to Android\'s multi-user mechanism, allowing other cloned users\' programs to be used under the main user.\n\n\n\n         1. From the menu bar in the upper right corner, you can obtain the local clone program user UID.\n\n         2. There is an option in the lower right corner that allows batch or individual selection of clone program user UIDs for deletion operations.\n\n         3. Below is the button to apply changes. Click it to allow selected or unselected clone program users to perform deletion operations.\n\n         4. Next to the menu above is a search button, do not click it.\n\n         5. Click the pattern in the upper left corner to return to the previous menu.</string>
    <string name="show_app_clone_low_version_msg">Android version 5.0 and below does not support the clone function.</string>
    <string name="button_home_run_cmd">RunCommand</string>
    <string name="run_cmd_run_bt">Run</string>
    <string name="run_cmd_input_cmd_str_hint">Please enter the command you want to execute</string>
    <string name="show_help_getRunCmdHELP">This interface is mainly used to execute the commands that come with the device, and all the operations done here are implemented in the ProcessBuilder service.\n\nEnter the command you want to execute in the edit box, and then click the button next to it to execute the command, and return the execution result in the blank interface below.\n</string>
    <string name="usb_button_select_local_img">Select Local Image File</string>
    <string name="permission_storage_grand">Access to the file has been granted.</string>
    <string name="general_loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="check_app_update">Checking for updates...</string>
    <string name="check_app_update_title">Check APP Update</string>
    <string name="check_app_update_is_ok">A new version has been detected, is it updated?</string>
    <string name="check_app_update_is_no">No updates detected.</string>
    <string name="app_clean_toast_msg">clean ok...</string>
    <string name="help_check_update_button">Chcek APP Update</string>
    <string name="help_clean_app_files_button">Clean APP Cache Files</string>
    <string name="help_open_source_global_button">Github Project</string>
    <string name="help_open_source_china_button">Gitee Project</string>
    <string name="clean_input_hint_tips">Please enter an integer</string>
    <string name="clean_input_time_second">second</string>
    <string name="clean_input_time_minute">minute</string>
    <string name="clean_input_time_hour">hour</string>
    <string name="clean_input_time_day">day</string>
    <string name="clean_input_value_tips">Pleas input value</string>
    <string name="copy_app_detail">Copy APP Detail</string>
    <string name="jump_app_detail">Jump APP Detail</string>
    <string name="add_clean_list">Add scheduled cleaning list</string>
    <string name="added_clean_list_msg">Is Added scheduled cleaning list!</string>
    <string name="show_clone_unock_max_user">Unlock Max Limit</string>
    <string name="show_clone_unock_max_user_tips_msg">After running this function, the device will soft reboot to unlock restrictions.</string>
    <string name="get_all_apps_by_clone">Fetching the list of all apps for the cloned user (including disabled ones, please wait...)</string>
    <string name="get_user_apps_by_clone">Retrieving the app list for the cloned user (including disabled apps, please wait...)</string>
    <string name="button_stop_share">Stop shareing</string>
</resources>